MUGABO Shafi Danny

Software developer

Kigali, Rwanda (+250) 781-567-627 mugabodannyshafi@gmail.com



SUMMARY

I am a talented Software Developer with over 2 years of experience building strong and scalable web applications. I enjoy turning new ideas into working solutions. Based in Kigali, Rwanda, I am focused on advancing technology and promoting digital innovation in my area.

EXPERIENCE

Andela, Kigali — Full-Stack Developer Intern

February 2024 - november 2024

Academic Bridge, Kigali — Backend Developer

August 2024 - Present

EDUCATION

GS NDP Cyanika, Nyamagabe — High School

January 2020 - August 2023 Software development

LANGUAGES

★ English: Fluent

★ Kinyarwanda: Native

SKILLS

JavaScript

Node.js

NestJS

ReactJS

Next.js

Typescript

Tailwind

CSS

HTML

SCSS

ExpressJs

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

MySQL

PHP

Git for version control

Shadcn Ui

Material Ui

Framer motion

GSAP

Jest

Sanity.io